articlepantry.com 2009-06-19

# Article Pantry - Submit articles, Promote your site, Internet Marketing

**ArticlePantry.com Privacy Policy**

ArticlePantry.com and its sister sites may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name & e-mail address) subject to the terms of the following privacy policy. ArticlePantry.com will never sell, barter, rent or give any of your contact information to any third party. Period.

**How we gather information from users**  
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase.

You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most web sites, ArticlePantry.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. 

> For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology (Via your IP Address.), to recognize you and hold information from your visit. 

Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. 

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information. 

> For example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences. 

**What we do with the information we collect**  
Like other web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and we do not share your information with anyone. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on ArticlePantry.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by ArticlePantry.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by ArticlePantry.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information.

We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**  
ArticlePantry.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. 

> For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a ArticlePantry.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. 

Also, through ArticlePantry.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. ArticlePantry.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. 

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. 

> For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. 

Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. ArticlePantry.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. 

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of ArticlePantry.com and this policy.

**Children**  
ArticlePantry.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about minors except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a minor in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe ArticlePantry.com has any information from or about a minor, please contact us through the contact page. 

|
